《女子监狱》
第二季第六集
我觉得爱是什么啊
What do I think love is?
看见他就让你觉得很紧张
It's like when someone makes your stomach feel all tight,
却又轻飘飘的  你懂吧
but floaty at the same time, you know?
脸都笑抽筋了
And your cheeks hurt from smiling.
一直笑得别人以为你有病
And you smile so much that people think something's wrong with you.
爱云淡风轻
Love is light.
是包容
Acceptance.
是激情
Fire.
痛苦
Pain.
刻骨铭心的痛苦
Horrible pain.
你却忍不住一再亲近
That you want again and again.
还有做爱
And also, fucking.
不间断深入地  操得下不了地
Twenty-four seven, deep-dick, can't-walk-right fucking.
我啊  一谈到爱情根本停不下来
Well, you know me. I got so much to say about love.
有一年啊  那个华尔街高富帅带我坐直升机去了华盛顿
And one year, this Wall Street guy flew me in a helicopter to D.C.
真的吗
For serious?
情人节男人干嘛都有可能  他们最爱这个节日了
Valentine's Day makes guys go crazy. They love it.
男人最恨情人节了
Men hate Valentine's Day.
至少看上去没有啊
They don't act like they hate it.
那是因为你长得美  跟索菲娅・沃加拉一样
That's because you look like Sofia Vergara.
《摩登家庭》女主角
她的胸倒货真价实
Them things is real.
有次我看见她在翠贝卡区跑步
I once saw her jogging in Tribeca.
伊恩好久没来看我了  他要是明天来看我就好了
Ian hasn't visited in so long. It'd be nice if he showed up tomorrow.
可他只有一辆小摩托  骑过来太冷了
But he's only got a Vespa and it's too cold to ride this far.
有一次亚迪尔送了我花  从他亲戚葬礼上顺的
One year, Yadriel got me flowers. He stole them from his cousin's funeral.
-好甜蜜呀  -拜托
- It was so sweet. - Please.
情人节就这样  要是不扮成完美情人
Valentine's Day was invented to make people feel like shit
就会死一样
if they're not part of some perfect couple.
没错
True.
迪艾保说这世上没有完美情人
Diablo says there are no perfect couples,
但每一对都各有其美
but each couple is perfect in its own way.
情人节还被关着  一定很难受吧
It must be hard. Being locked up on Valentine's Day.
没别的意思
That's all.
谢谢  费歇尔  你真为我们着想
Aw. Thank you, Fischer. That was really empathetic of you.
-要来块饼干吗  -好啊  谢谢
- You want a cookie? - Oh, sure. Thank you.
-你要喝点水吗  费歇尔  -没事
- You need some water, Fischer? - No. I'm fine.
就知道她没口活过
I knew she didn't swallow.
嗨
Hi.
你明晚订了哪里
Where'd you make reservations for tomorrow night?
什么
Wait, what?
我正假装我们是一对情人啊
I'm trying to pretend like we're a normal couple.
这样啊
Oh.
我在洛伦佐餐厅订了两个座位
Um, well, I got us a table for two at Lorenzo's.
就在壁炉旁
The one by the fireplace.
等不及给你看我的新裙子
I can't wait for you to see my dress.
很性感却不浪荡
It's sexy, but not slutty, you know?
迫不及待
I can't wait to see it.
再给去我拿包面粉好吗
Mamita, can you get me another bag of flour?
给你
Here.
-这是啥  -是清单
- What's this? - It's a list.
要哄你的岳母开心啊  知道吗
Wanna keep the mother-in-law happy, right?
我想着或许可以借用一下你的假肢
I figured I might as well make use of Sleepy Hollow
免得再节外生枝
before the other shoe drops.
明白吗
Get it?
由于无法避免的维修因素  淋浴要限制在30秒内
这就是维给我们争取来的  用这种破龙头洗澡
So this is what Vee negotiated for us? Using these broke-ass showers?
-这什么破谈判啊  -你说呢
- Man, that's some broke-ass negotiation. - You think?
你们知道洗澡时间太长对人不好吧
You do know that long showers are bad for you.
对表皮细胞什么不好
Mess with your keratinocytes and whatnots.
苏珊娜  你他妈给我闭嘴
Hey, Suzanne? Shut the fuck up.
为什么要我离开图书馆
Yeah, why the hell would I leave the library?
那是监狱里最好的工作了
It's the best job here.
因为那儿钱少  付不了房租  吃不上红酒牛肉
Because books do not pay the rent. Books do not bourguignon the beef.
我们有大生意要做
We are starting something.
我不想去保管处
I don't wanna join custodial.
-但我还是想要你去  -不行  我不去
- And yet I am still asking you. - No way. No.
-快点快点  -给我闭嘴
- Oh, come on. Come on! - Shut up!
当年你跑过来跟我说
You know what? Do you know how easy it would've been
"维  把我从教养院弄出去吧"
for me to say no when you came to me and said,
我完全可以不帮你  知道吗
"Vee, get me out of this group home"?
"我不想再见到那寄养父亲的狗脸了"
"Save me from this sick fuck-faced foster father I got!" Huh?
-这不公平  -公平  醒醒吧
- That's not fair. - Fair? Girl, please.
哪有什么公平  你以为是排排坐吃果果
Fair's where you go get you some cotton candy.
坐着旋转木马吗
Where you ride the Tilt-A-Whirl.
我在找杰克
I'm looking for Jack.
他不在这儿
He's not here.
他每年都给我买巧克力
He buys me chocolates every year.
我们有固定的收入
We're on a fixed income, of course.
但他说今晚要喂鸭子
But he's gotta treat his Duckie right, he says.
要是他找不到我  那就浪费了
And if he can't find me, they'll be wasted.
操  我要是变这样  就直接掐死我
Fuck. Kill me in my sleep if I ever get like that.
听着  你给我好好想想  然后照我说的做
Look. You're gonna think about it, right? And then you gonna do as I say.
痛啊
Ah!
就是很放松  懂吗
It's just chilling, you know?
跟人一起玩  开些很冷的玩笑啊
Kicking it with somebody, talking, making mad stupid jokes.
一点都不想睡觉
And, like, not even wanting to go to sleep,
这样就会有那么段时间见不到对方
'cause then you might be without 'em for a minute.
而你一刻都不想分开
And you don't want that.
美国陆军  霍恩菲尔兹驻地  多国战备中心  德国  巴伐利亚
一  二  三  开始
Ein, zwei, drei, go!
就快...
And...
好了  谁下一个  谁下一个
And done! Who's next? Who's next?
厉害
Whoo!
你赢不了我的
You can't beat me.
我不可超越
I am untouchable.
可我觉得你很亲近
I think you are very touchable.
找间屋子好吗
Get a room.
说德语  白痴  再说一遍
German, fool. Talk it.
是"旁建"  "旁间"
Zing? Zinger?
是"房间"  你好歹住在这里  尊重它的语言
Das Zimmer. You're part of a community. Respect its language.
我爸才是这圈子的
My father's part of a community.
我不过是他随你们四处反恐时
I'm the unfortunate appendage he drags about
携带的一个拖油瓶而已
wherever your fight against terror takes him.
他在说傻话
He's just talkin' smack.
那你这些年搬过多少次家
How many times have you had to move in your short little life?
数不清了
Too many.
但是我不会再搬了  我爸答应我了
But this is the end of the road. My pops promised.
怎么用德语说
How do you say,
"我真想看你们俩做女女之爱啊"
"I'd like to watch as you two make sweet, sweet lady love," in German?
没门  混蛋  没门
Nein, motherfucker. Nein.
这活儿太操蛋了
This job is bullshit.
哪有  这是道有奖励的考验题
No. 'Tis a rewarding puzzle.
哪儿来的考验  就是收拾电器
Ain't no puzzle. Makes electrical look good.
真不敢相信我竟然听了那老婊子的话
Can't believe I let that old bitch talk me into this.
你还是别背后指摘帕克小姐的不是
I wouldn't speak ill of Miss Parker's methods.
她耳里肯定听不得这些话
She wouldn't tolerate such words.
听着  沃森有权利
Hey, now, Watson got the right
表达她对新工作的不满
to express her discomfort for her new job.
就算你觉得打扫卫生没什么问题
Just because cleaning quiets your discombobulation
不代表别人就都一样
doesn't mean it does so for everyone.
说得好  扫把  说得好
Point well made, Moppet. Point well made.
你真是蠢
You such a dumbass.
沃森  你看着很累啊
Hey, Watson, you look a little tired.
要不我晚些时候去给你按摩下股四头肌
Maybe I could come by later and massage your quads?
他妈给我滚远点
Get the fuck out of here.
不管你们这里要干什么勾当
You know, whatever y'all got going on in here.
接手了保管处  我都要分一杯羹
You know, taking over custodial. I want a piece.
我会睁只眼闭只眼  这样什么都看不见
I use it to cover my eyes. That way, you know, I won't see anything.
明晚  我会用我的手  让你的情人节爽歪歪
Tomorrow night, I'm going to put the "V" in your Valentine.
没错  尽情操我
That's right. Fuck me.
沃伦  谁陪你过今年的情人节
Hey, Warren, who gonna be your Valentine this year?
你不总是去勾搭谁吗
You always battin' them freaky blacks at somebody.
不不
Oh, no.
今年我要爱一个值得我爱的人  真的
No, this year I'm loving someone who deserves me. Me.
废物
Loser.
闭嘴
Shut up!
无所谓了  要我说  这是一年中最难过的时刻
Whatever. Depressing-ass time of year, you ask me.
妈的
Motherfucker!
我操  你尿裤子了
Shit. You pissed your pants?
我去给你找块尿布
I'm gonna go find you a diaper.
请注意  探访时间开始
Your attention, please. Visiting hours are now open.
所有犯人均可进入探访室
All prisoners are free to go to the visiting room.
明天是佛罗伦萨・亨德森的生日
Tomorrow's Florence Henderson's birthday!
什么
What?
情人节啊  是佛罗伦萨・亨德森的生日
Valentine's Day. Florence Henderson's birthday!
我们每年都有裸体庆祝派对
We should be having our annual naked Brady-thon celebration
我会伴着阳光天乐队的歌跳脱衣舞
and I should be doing some kind of a striptease to Sunshine Day.
也许...也许...再抹点油
And then maybe something... Maybe something with Wesson Oil, that...
帕波
Piper.
你好
Hi.
嗨
我听说了你奶奶的事
I heard about your grandma.
莱瑞
Larry...
我想要我的家
I want my home.
从这儿出去后
When I get out of here,
我想回家
I wanna come home.
这可不是小事啊
That's quite the statement.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
我不是在问你
Well, I'm not asking you.
我是在问未来的帕波  那个重获自由的帕波
I'm asking Future Piper. Free Piper.
你能保证你依旧想回家吗
Can you guarantee that you still will?
未来的帕波希望能回家
Future Piper hopes so.
可是现今的莱瑞不能靠希望活着
Present Larry can't live on hope.
我可以靠吃芥末豆花生黄油饼干
Wasabi peas and peanut butter pretzels, apparently,
但希望是不够的
but not hope.
拜托别在这儿提这些东西
Please don't mention those things
除非你藏了什么东西要给我
unless you're hiding some up your butt for me.
帕波
Piper,
有个《都市邮报》的记者  安德鲁・南斯
this reporter from CityPost, Andrew Nance.
他...
He, um...
问我这里是否有资金异常的问题
He asked me about financial irregularities here.
比如凭空出现的销售商  从未建起的楼等
Uh... Vendors that don't exist, buildings that were never built.
于是我就想  "去你妈的
And I was like, "Fuck that.
为什么要他写  我来写"
"Why should he write it? I'll write it."
写什么
Write what?
一篇文章  靠你从内部挖掘信息
An article. With you investigating from the inside.
新闻自由权并非只有自由人才有  是吧
Freedom of the press shouldn't only be a privilege of the free, right?
-你觉得怎么样  -天哪
- What do you say? - Oh, my God.
我的天  莱瑞  我的上帝
Oh, my God, Larry. Jesus Christ!
-怎么了  -你又来了
- What... - You're doing it again!
你说什么啊
What are you talking about?
我们要曝光这个地方  帕波
We'll fucking expose this place, Piper.
你就是月亮  莱瑞  不要再做月亮了
You're the moon, Larry. You have got to stop being the moon!
月亮怎么了
What's wrong with being the moon?
它不能自己发光
It doesn't have its own light.
是啊  怎么了  那你就是太阳了
So, right. So, what? That makes you the sun?
你就是太阳了  是不是啊  帕波
Are you the sun, Piper? Huh?
你是全太阳系的中心
You're the center of the solar system
而我就是块毫无生气的石头
and I'm just a dead hunk of crap rock!
帕波  你的一切依旧到处都是
How am I supposed to become my own planet, Piper,
我要怎么成为独立的星球
when your shit is still everywhere?
你倒是往前看了
You get to move on.
你还操了艾丽克斯或是谁  我却止步不前
You get to fuck Alex or whoever's next, and I'm stuck.
我深陷在你的衣服鞋子里
I'm stuck with your sweaters and your shoes
还有他妈什么丝芙兰代销店淘来的东西
and your goddamn Sephora fucking outlet store worth of products!
你无处不在
You are everywhere.
就像活在石棺里
It's like living inside a sarcophagus.
要是我的东西太碍事了你可以送去波丽那儿
Well, take my stuff to Polly's if it's so in your way.
还有你其实是想说"陵墓"而不是"石棺"
And you mean "mausoleum," not "sarcophagus."
不要再对我指手画脚了
Don't tell me what I mean!
至少人们还能在月亮上行走
At least people can walk on the moon.
太阳呢  一靠近就只会燃成灰烬
Anyone gets near the sun, they burn right up.
维说她年纪大了  我才不信呢
Vee says she's too old. Don't believe it for a second!
那女的曾经怎么对我啊
What that woman did to me...
江山易改本性难移
People don't change.
你能不能快点啊
Hurry it up, will you?
我尽力了妈  火星溅得我脸都疼
I'm trying, Ma. The sparks are burning my cheeks!
那就把头转过去  你哥呢
Then turn your head! Where's your brother?
他有幽闭恐惧症  呆在林子里守着入口呢
He got claustrophobic. He's in the woods, guarding the entrance.
妈妈  我好难过啊
I'm just so sad, mamochka.
真遗憾她离你而去  瓦斯里
I'm sorry she left you, Vasily,
但我相信你也是活该
but I'm sure you did something to deserve it.
我以前会看她入睡
I used to watch her sleep
祈祷我能强大起来  不再毁掉一切  妈妈
and pray for the strength to stop ruining everything, Ma.
那有用吗
And how did that work out for you?
今天不做工  明天再来
No work today. Come back tomorrow.
杰克说他会在这儿
Jack said he would be out here.
我看他上了辆出租车
I saw him get into a taxi.
出租车  就在外面吗
A taxi? Out here?
真不可思议
Imagine that.
谢谢你  女士
Thank you, young lady.
你能不能快点啊
Hurry it up, will you?
妈妈
Mama!
受够了你恶心的抱怨
You and your disgusting whining!
想要你的女人回来  就去追
If you want your woman back, go get her.
赶紧把东西递给我  快点
Now hand up the shit. Come on!
等你出去时
When you get out of here...
想过家里会有谁等着你吗
who do you imagine yourself going home to?
《犯罪》里的费欧娜・艾波
Fiona Apple in the Criminal video.
问得太傻了
Stupid question.
你呢
What about you?
我一直以为是莱瑞
I always thought it would be Larry,
如今看来得重新考虑了
but I think it's time to re-imagine.
这个愚蠢操蛋的节日
This stupid fucking holiday.
你要是愿意  我能让你忘记这一天
Listen, if you want, I can help you forget what day it is.
甚至是你的名字
You know, or your name, for that matter.
你也知道我的答案  不要
You know, no.
我不想在你的做爱比赛里
I am not interested in being a prize,
做一个价码低得不可思议的战利品
albeit a shockingly-undervalued one, in your little sex game.
好吧
Fine.
我失去了我爱操纵人  漂亮又变态的前任
I lost my manipulative, gorgeous, psychopath ex
又失去了我贴心又有点不着边的未婚夫
and my sweet, kind, unfocused fiance.
我没有家了
I don't have a home anymore.
不  查普曼  你有
Yeah, Chapman, you do.
这傻逼电线
This shit pile.
真他妈甜蜜啊
Home sweet home.
听着  我不得不承认
Look, I gotta say,
你那不着边的未婚夫说的什么文章  还真有点道理
your unfocused fiance is on the right track with this article shit.
我都不知道多少次修这个仪表板的短路了
I mean, this is like my 20th time trying to fix a short in this panel alone.
根本没人花钱管
Nobody's spending money here.
加列戈说你找我
Hey. Gallego said you were looking for me?
乔  这些通话  真是太有意思了
Joe, these phone calls. They're amazing!
听这个
Listen.
我说看着他  不是操他
I said to keep an eye on him, not fuck him!
不过是菊花入而已  不算的呀
It was only in the ass. That don't count.
我要告诉妈妈
I'm telling Mom.
这么劲爆
Whoa.
是吧  太有意思了  这么多不同的生活
I know! Anyway. It's so interesting. All these lives.
就跟读狄更斯似的
It's like reading Dickens!
不错  这挺积极的
It's good. Showing initiative.
也许这样菲格就不会再盯着我了
Maybe it'll help get Fig off my ass.
你知道她要求我执行记过配额吗
You know she asked me to impose a shot quota?
太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
你能站出来对抗她真厉害
I love that you stand up to her.
你跟那谁怎么样了
So, how are things going with... What's his name?
他们不去了  他穿太多背心了
They're not going. He wore a lot of vests.
这样
Ah.
也挺常见的
Well, that happens.
哦对了  我在一个乐队里...
You know, I play in this band...
你玩乐队啊
You're in a band? Wow!
是啊
Yeah?
就是小打小闹
Yeah. It's no big deal.
明晚我们有演出  你要不要来
We play in town tomorrow night. You wanna come?
我要看着情人节派对
Oh, I'm working the Valentine's party.
我能帮你调开
I'll get you off.
帮你调开值班时间
I'll get you off the schedule.
可以帮你换班  小事情
I can get your shift covered. It's fine.
我挺喜欢听音乐的  一定很棒
Well, I do love music! That'd be awesome.
-谢谢  -那好
- Thanks. - Great.
-那到时候见  -好
- I'll see you there then! - Okay.
我在海滋客工作时和我老板有过一腿
I had this thing with my boss at Long John Silver's.
后来我发现他老婆超级辣
And then I found out his wife was wicked hot.
所以感觉还不错
So that was nice.
"你怎么知道我不开心"  爱丽丝说
"'How do you know I'm mad? ' said Alice.
"一看就知道"  猫说  "不然你也不会来这里"
"'You must be, ' said the Cat, 'or you wouldn't have come here.'"
你真他妈对
Mmm. Shit. You right.
路易斯・卡罗一定蹲过牢
Lewis Carroll must have gone to prison.
RJ的妈妈就叫爱丽丝
RJ's mom was named Alice.
是吗  她也掉进兔子洞了
Oh, yeah? She fall down a rabbit hole?
-不是  是毒窟  -这样
- No. A crack hole. - Ah.
然后她发现一块石头  上面写着"吸了我"
She found a little rock. Said "Smoke me," on it.
这不好笑  那东西很厉害
That's not funny. That shit was serious.
"吸了我"  真有你的
"Smoke me." You a dumbass.
杰弗逊  赶紧说再见吧  你得去保管处了
Jefferson. Say goodbye. You're on custodial now.
现在就要去了
Already?
-什么  你要走了  -是啊
- Wait. You leaving? - Yeah.
还记得我跟你说维在策划什么事吗
Remember, I told you Vee was getting something together?
但是你为什么要离开图书馆呢  你喜欢这里
But why would you leave the library, man? You know you love it here.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我欠她
I owe her.
她或许也能把你换过去吧
She could probably get you transferred, I bet.
不会的
Nah.
我自己心里有数
No, I know when I got it good.
好吧  那我们晚饭见了
Okay. Well, I'll see you at dinner.
怎么样
Anything?
再高点
Higher maybe.
等等
Wait.
腿抽筋了
Leg cramp.
抱歉
Sorry.
好了
Okay.
太棒了
That's nice.
-是吗  -嗯
- Yeah? Yeah? - Yeah.
不行
No.
没感觉了
It's gone.
就跟你说交叉式行不通
I told you scissoring wasn't a thing.
说到爱情  有这么一句话
There's a saying about love.
关于爱情有好多句话呢
There's a million sayings about love.
我想到了其中一句
I'm thinking of the one that says,
"爱不是互相凝视对方
"Love is not about staring at each other,
而是望向同一个方向"
but staring off in the same direction."
我不喜欢这句
I don't like that one.
我更喜欢看着你
I love staring at you too much.
我渴了
I'm thirsty.
我给你擦
Let me get that.
很好
Oh, yeah.
我还要
More.
搞什么
What the fuck?
-不过是这个而已  -在违禁物清单上
- Just this. - It's on the list.
-只是水烟  -少来  艾丽卡
- It's fucking vapor! - Give me a break, Eliqua.
卡普托今天盯着我  放回车里去  下一个
Caputo's up my ass today. Put it in your car. Next.
现在搜身是强制的了
Pat-downs are mandatory now.
跟你开玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
才不想碰你的假肢呢
I don't wanna touch that peg-leg shit.
情人节快乐  下一个
Happy Valentine's Day. Next.
看看这些破玩意儿
Look at this shit.
幸好你长得漂亮
You're lucky you're pretty. You know that, right?
这个上面写了啥
What does that one say?
"伊恩"  以防万一他来了  我真傻
"Ian." In case he shows up today. Stupid.
妈逼
Shit.
真高兴我们是一家人
I'm so glad we're family.
-情人节快乐  -谢谢
- Happy Valentine's Day. - Thanks.
今天有给我做什么爱心晚餐吗
Are you cooking up something special for me today?
屋子里闻着真香
The house smells great.
这就是你想要我做的吗
That's what you're gonna expect me to do?
给你做饭  当你的家庭主妇
Cook for you? Be your little housewife?
别想了  不可能
It's not happening.
没有  我以为我们是在扮演...
No. I thought we were playing the...
我无所谓你煮不煮饭
I don't care if you cook.
抱歉  我今天心情不太好
Sorry. I've just been depressed today.
不想再玩装正常的游戏了
I don't want to play the normal game anymore
因为我们永远不可能像正常情侣那样
'cause I don't know how we ever are gonna be normal.
就是想告诉你  如果你想找人说说话
Well, just so you know. Counselors can be a great resource
或哭一场  你可以找辅导员
if you feel like you need to talk or cry or something.
-谁是你辅导员  -海利
- Who'd you get? - Healy.
这样
Oh.
-有什么不对吗  -没有
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
我只是觉得没有哪个姑娘真心喜欢他
I just get the sense that none of the girls really like him.
但你很坚强  都会过去的
But you're tough, you'll be fine.
你有没有觉得最近我们烧断了很多保险丝
Have you noticed we've been blowing a lot of fuses around here lately?
你才发现这儿都快散架了吗
You're just noticing this place is falling apart?
监狱难道没有基础设施的预算吗
Doesn't the prison have a budget for infrastructure?
当然有
Sure.
那上个季度的电器预算哪去了
And what happened to the electrical budget from last quarter?
说是要加护A区栅栏和卸货平台
It went to "upgrading the A block grid and loading dock panel."
真的吗  我们真加护了
Really? We did that?
预算报告是这么写的
That's what the budget report says.
-那我们做了吗  -这个嘛
- So we did it? - Okay.
-真加护了吗  -不然呢
- So it happened? - Why not?
我不明白
I don't understand.
相信我  你不想懂的
Trust me. You don't want to.
好了  时间到了  恭喜你刚挣了11分
Congratulations. Hour's up. You just earned another 11 cents.
好  各位  海豚式
All right, everybody. Dolphin pose.
我觉得我能帮你完成这个海豚式
You know, I think I can help you with the dolphin pose.
关键就在于保证你的骨盆放在...
The trick is to make sure that your pelvic basin is just right...
离我远点
Get away from me.
我去  谢谢红妈
No way! Thanks, Red.
红妈  上帝保佑你
Red! Bless you!
现在  再做一次海豚式
Now, let's return to dolphin pose.
茎茶
Kukicha tea.
看看谁回来了
Well, look who's back.
无意打扰  姑娘们  继续你们的海豚吧
Sorry to interrupt, girls. Continue with your dolphins.
操  刚搞了个4分的
Fuck, just bagged a four-pointer.
我们差不多平手
We're almost tied.
听着
Listen up.
不要再毫无意义地赌气了
This angry nonsense has to stop.
很快我们就需要互相帮助
We're going to need each other soon.
所有人
All of us.
我没开玩笑  尼古拉斯
I'm not kidding, Nicky.
我们必须团结一致  这样才能更强大
We have to stick together. We're stronger together.
所以你就想再收买她们
So you try to buy their love back?
谢谢红妈
Thanks, Red.
干嘛要问我
Why are you asking me that?
你不该和我说话  你不该...
You shouldn't be talking to me. So... You shouldn't be...
-14罐护足粉  -有了
- Fourteen foot powders. - Check.
-20管牙膏  -有了
- Twenty Effergrips. - Check that.
还记得我们卖烟那会儿么
Remember when we sold smokes?
我发誓我再也不投给自由党了
God, I swear I'm gonna vote Libertarian.
我得去趟车里  等会儿就回来
I gotta run to my car. I'll be right back.
我能出去一会儿么
Mind if I step out for a moment?
我他妈才不管呢
I don't give a shit.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
"维  你把美味姐弄去保管处我很不爽"
"Yo, Vee, I'm just so mad since y'all got Taystee transferred to custodial.
"这样我只能一个人在图书馆玩儿奶了"
"Just left me in the library with my titties in my hand."
猜对了吗
Close?
你漏了一句
No, you left out,
"要是你害她惹麻烦  我就杀了你"
"If you get her in trouble, I'll kill you."
-真的  -你试试
- Really? - Bet.
-你要怎么杀我呢  -我会想到办法的
- And how would you kill me? - I'll figure it out.
我知道她觉得自己欠了你  可我明白
I know she thinks she owes you, but from what I heard,
你不过是个利用迷途小孩  只顾自己的恶霸
you're just a bully who uses lost kids for her own shit
等他们没用了就扔到一边
and then dumps 'em soon as the heat comes down.
你他妈就是个吸血鬼
You're a fucking vampire.
曾经有个小孩  叫哈罗・琼斯
There was this kid growing up. Name was Haro Jones.
他那双手臂啊  我喜欢得...
He had these arms. I just wanted to...
只想从上舔到下...
lick the length of his arms.
有一天我在公园里
And then one day I walked into the park.
看见他手伸进杰米拉・拉金的裙子里
Found his hand up Jamela Larkin's skirt.
真是伤透了我的心
Broke my poor fool heart.
听着女人  我他妈才不管你过去的故事...
Look, lady, I don't give a fuck about your little stories and shit...
美味姐...
Taystee...
永远...
will...
不会...
never...
喜欢...
love...
你
you.
她永远不会喜欢你
She will never love you.
不是你想要的那种
Not the way you want.
我不需要她喜欢我
Yo, I don't want her like that.
我只想照顾她  仅此而已
I'm just looking out for her. That's all.
爸爸  他妈几个中国兵在我窗外抽烟来着
Yo, Pops, some fucking Chinese soldiers was just smoking right outside my window.
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
怎么了  妈妈呢
What? Where's Mom?
她没事
She's fine.
我们被调回美国了
We're being transferred back to the States.
我也不知道为什么  但已经定了
I don't know why, but we are.
什么
What?
抱歉
Sorry.
让你失望了  珀比
I let you both down, P.
我也不知该说什么好
I don't know what to say.
在这儿了
All right.
天哪...
Jesus! The...
你越界了  查普曼
You're out of bounds, Chapman.
你不说出去  我就不说
Well, I won't tell if you don't.
把我们当犯人一样对待
Treating us like we're prisoners.
我听说这里曾经想建个体育馆
Hey, you know, I heard that there were plans to build a gym here.
你知道后来怎么样了吗
Do you know whatever happened to that?
还不是老样子
What always happens.
我来接手吧
I'll take it from here.
就是找一根出问题的电线
Just looking for a faulty wire.
为什么要问麦克斯韦体育馆的事
Why are you asking Maxwell about a gym?
听说最近你的问题有点多啊
From what I hear, you're full of questions lately.
你知道的  我一直很关心
You know that I have always been interested
他人的安全与健康
in the health and safety of others.
我还努力帮你去看你奶奶
I'm trying to help you with your nana.
所以我再问一遍  为什么你问这些问题
So again, why are you asking all these questions?
"新闻自由权并非只有自由人才有"
"Freedom of the press shouldn't only be a privilege of the free."
这他妈扯什么犊子
What the fuck does that mean?
关新闻什么事
What does the press have anything to do with this?
我想开办一份监狱简报
I'm starting a prison newsletter.
-一份简报  -对
- A newsletter? - A newsletter.
一份...由犯人撰写的...简报
A newsletter... written by the prisoners...
由文章和专栏组成
with articles and op-ed pieces.
所以我试着走出自己的世界
That is why I've been trying to get out of my bubble
开始了解这个地方
and get to know this place.
我们...这里是我们的家
We... This is our home.
我们应该加强彼此之间的交流
We should all be communicating more.
犯人啊  守卫啊  管理人员
Inmates, guards, administration.
这份简报可以帮助
This could really,
我们更了解彼此  了解这里
really help us get to know each other and this place better.
当然需要您的同意
Pending your approval, of course,
主编大人
Mr. Editor-in-Chief.
别捧过头了
Don't oversell it.
-一份简报  -对
- A newsletter? - Mmm.
好吧  不是说我同意了
Okay. I'm not saying yes.
明天给我几篇例文看看
Show me some sample stories by tomorrow.
明天  当然可以
Tomorrow? Sure. Okay. Yeah.
以前姑娘们都很喜欢我
The girls used to like me.
她们还会喜欢你的
They will again.
我的姑娘们都怎么样
Hey, hey, hey. How my girls doing?
怎么又板起脸了
Why you got your famous pouty face on?
我不明白你在干嘛
I don't understand what you doing.
是吗  有多少次你都不理解我在干嘛
Yeah? And how many times have you not understood my methods
最终不都搞懂了
only to have everything be made clear?
是吗  那警察追RJ那次呢
Yeah, like when the cops were after RJ?
这么早就放大招了
God damn! You done gone for the nuclear option early.
为什么你不愿意谈RJ
Why don't you ever wanna talk about RJ?
库兹尼克夫妇诚邀您参加他们女儿
安吉拉・库兹尼克和克里斯托弗・麦克拉伦的婚礼
2月14日周五  下午4点
因为都过去了  姑娘
Because it's in the past, girl.
而我活在现在  你也应该这样
I live in the now. So should you.
一整天我都他妈在洗厕所  为你辩护
All damn day I've been scrubbing toilets, defending you.
可我都不再相信你了
And I don't even believe in you anymore!
-美味  -不
- Taystee. - No!
你没有任何计划
You don't have a plan.
你只是想证明你还能使唤我
You just wanna prove that you can order me around.
但是不行  不行了
But no, not anymore.
-打开箱子  -什么
- Open the box. - What?
打开箱子
Open the box.
妈的  我告诉你  我不想再保洁了
Man, I told you. I'm done cleaning.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
什么  烟草
What? Tobacco?
清洁剂去哪儿了
But where's the cleanser?
艾・沃
就好像是踏进浴缸
Okay, it's like getting into a bath,
水就像温暖的巧克力布丁
but the water is like warm chocolate pudding.
还有史密斯乐队演奏《今夜不眠》
And The Smiths are playing There Is a Light That Never Goes Out.
到处都是暖暖的灯光
Oh. There's warm lighting all over
五个男人帮你按摩
and there're like five dudes massaging you.
而且你还有个披萨
And you have a pizza.
她说的没错  你还有个披萨
She's right. And you also have a pizza.
我从那个有胡子的希腊妞那儿弄了点私酒
Hey, I got some hooch from that Greek chick with the beard.
-真不错哎  -是吧
- That's pretty good! - Yeah?
费歇尔今天外出  有自己的活动
Fischer's out today. Apparently having her woman time.
是嘛
Oh.
乔呢
Where's Joe?
他也不在
He's out, too.
让这些姑娘开什么派对
Let 'em have their stupid little party
又不留足够人手管理
and then don't put enough muscle on.
太典型了
So typical.
布罗尼科斯基  控制着点
Bronikowski, leave room for Jesus.
不然我分分钟就关了派对
I will shut this thing down in a heartbeat.
你说好不好笑
You know what's funny?
虽然我在女子监狱工作
I'm in a women's prison,
可我却一点都不了解女人
but I don't understand women at all.
我告诉你  本尼特
I'll tell you something about women, Bennett.
女人啊  你要让她们觉得你投入了很多感情
With women, you make 'em think you're meeting them halfway,
可实际上呢
when really what you're doing is
你只投入了10%到15%
you're meeting them about 10% to 15% of the way.
女人数学都不好  记住这点
Women are really bad at math. Don't forget that.
我会的  先生
I won't, sir.
-杰克有打电话吗  -谁
- Did Jack call yet? - Who?
听我说  达娅
Listen, Daya.
虽然我们没法做平常情侣  但是...
I know we can't be normal, but...
别说了
Shh.
带我出去  现在
Take me somewhere. Now.
她们更大了
Wow. They're bigger!
快点
Let's go.
怎么了
What is this?
嘿
Yo!
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
-为什么  -闭上
- What? Why? - Close 'em.
张开嘴
Open your lips.
少张点
Less.
-美味...  -快点
- T... - Do it.
什么  香烟
What? What's this? A cigarette?
要做生意了  珀比  维拟定好了销售计划
We in business, P! Vee's got a whole sales plan.
我们有报酬  我跟你说
We getting paid! I told you.
要有钱了啊
Next-level Mr. Miyagi shit, son!
让你爸爸想办法啊
Tell your father to fight!
没用的
Won't help.
是你爸想要我们走
Your father wants us gone,
我们就得走
we're gone.
那我和你一起走
Then I'm coming with you.
你不会喜欢新泽西的
Don't think Jersey's for you.
我爱你  珀比
I love you, Poussey.
听着
Look.
操你很爽
You're fun to fuck,
不过也就这样了
but that's it.
你是我一生所爱
You're the love of my life.
你的奶子真心不错  我会记住的
You have killer tits. I'll remember those.
昨天你还说你爱我
Yesterday you loved me!
怎么今天就这样了
How can you just shut down like that?
我是老手了
I've had a lot of practice.
真是意想不到的惊喜
Well, that was unexpected.
抱歉我之前心情不好
Sorry. I was in a mood before.
你真贴心
You're the sweetest man.
给你
Here.
还有条狗
Look at the dog!
真棒
This is so great.
你的也很棒啊
So was this.
这个
Mmm. This.
干嘛偷偷摸摸的
Sneaky, sneaky man.
致我的爱人
情人节快乐  那对小孩就是我们  情人节快乐  马上就能快乐  你知道我是谁
你看  我们也能成为普通情侣
See? We can be a normal couple.
不过你把"情"字写错了
Except you misspelled "Valentine's."
不  我不会
No, I didn't.
是门德斯写的
Mendez did.
你们好
Hi.
我们准备创办一份简报
I was wondering if I could ask you a few questions
所以能问你们几个问题吗
for a newsletter we're starting.
办简报  祝你们好运
A newsletter? Okay, good luck.
你看  今天是情人节
So, since it's Valentine's Day,
你觉得爱是什么
what is love to you?
你们怎么定义爱
How would you define love?
这问题真他妈蠢
That's a retarded fucking question.
好吧
Okay. Um...
换个问题
How about this?
上一次你们见到
When was the last time
大规模的水管修缮是什么时候
you saw any major plumbing work being done around here?
我想想
Hmm.
-大概04  05年吧  -04  05年
- '04-'05, maybe? - '04-'05.
有个叫唐娜・库索的胖妞一周内弄坏了三个马桶
This fatso named Donna Cusio broke three toilets in one week.
真他妈一团糟啊
It was a mess, man.
我想也是  太肥了肯定
I bet. Big, big woman.
我是卡佳  请留言
This is Katya. Leave a message.
宝贝
Hi, honey.
是我
It's me.
我打来就是想祝你情人节快乐
I just wanted to call and wish you a happy Valentine's Day.
你愿意
Would you like...
和我
to dance...
跳支舞吗
with me?
我是为你学的
I learned that for you.
我是一个好男人  卡佳  你会明白的
I'm a good man, Katya. You'll see that.
我一定会让你自豪能嫁给我这个傻蛋
I'm gonna make you really proud to be married to this big galoot.
我发誓
I swear to...
什么叫菲利斯不存在
The fuck you mean there's no Ferris?
说的是《春天不是读书天》的情节
听我说
No, okay. Hear me out.
菲利斯只是
Ferris is just a projection
卡梅隆假想出来的  表现他不敢反抗专横的爸爸
of Cameron's inability to stand up to his domineering father.
但问题就在这里  卡梅隆根本没离开过房间
But here's the mind-fuck. Cameron never actually leaves his room!
记得吗  他病了
Remember, he's sick.
于是他想象出一个理想化的自己  菲利斯
He invents this idealized self, Ferris.
还给他弄了个三十岁的女朋友
Plus his, like, 30-year-old girlfriend.
然后想象出了之后一系列的冒险
And then imagines this epic adventure
追车  游行  打球等等
with car chases, parades, ball games, blah, blah, blah.
所以逃学的一天
So this day off
只是他身体与意识的脱离...
is actually just the day off from his rigid coherence to mind-body alignment...
你他妈就不能给我闭嘴吗
Would you please shut the fuck up?
抱歉  只是我看的一个理论而已
Sorry. It's just a theory I read.
下次直接坐她脸上  她就闭嘴了
Next time, just sit on her face. It shuts her right up.
我会记住的
I'll keep that in mind.
为什么故意不理我
Why are you ignoring me?
为什么不理我  说啊
Why are you ignoring me? Spit it out! Come on!
你之前一直独裁这个小团体
Look, you've been lording over this group
就跟希拉里一样
like some Hillary Clinton dictator.
-什么  -可我们想要民主
- What? - And we wanna be a democracy.
你说我是希拉里・克林顿
Are you calling me Hillary Clinton?
要是你也穿得下裤套装
If the pantsuit fits.
听着  我们不带你玩了
Look, we're done with you. Right?
你们不带我了
Y'all are done with me?
真是搞笑啊  琳恩
That's really funny. That's really funny, Leanne.
如果我是希拉里
'Cause if I'm Hillary Clinton,
那你们就是贱人  毒鬼  只知道喝思乐冰
then y'all must be some sister-wife, tweaker, Slurpee-drinking,
没文化  没爹的拖车瘪三
fourth-grade reading level, Daddy-on-COPS, trailer trash nothing!
你们知道吗  我无所谓
And you know what? It's okay
因为你们从来对我都不算什么
'cause you ain't never even challenged me anyway.
其实  你们谁都不行
Actually, you know what? None of you did. Not one.
你老是和比你差的人打网球
You keep playing tennis with someone worse than you
你就永远打不好  所以谢谢
and you ain't never gonna get better. So thank you.
-你还打网球  -这是比喻  你个傻逼
- You play tennis? - It's a metaphor, you potato with eyes!
不好意思要说脏话了  你们吃屎去吧
You know what? Pardon my French, but you can eat my shit.
婊子
Whore.
婊子  婊子
Whore. Whore.
刚才可真尴尬
Man, that was awkward.
-安琪  -嗯
- Angie? - Yeah?
给我拿点饮料
Go get me some punch.
派对不错
Great party.
听着  我们很高兴
Listen, we are so happy
你和达娅有如此美好秘密的特殊时光
that you and Daya are having such fun, special, secret times together.
我们也很欣赏你对她这么好
And we really admire you providing for her so well.
尽管是这种情况
You know, despite the circumstances.
我们只想让你知道
And we just wanted to let you know
我们将以沉默来表达对你的完全支持
that we support you 500% with our continued silence.
鉴于如此  下次你再夹带私货进来时
Considering as such, in your next round of leg-based contraband,
我们有几个要求
we had a couple requests
这样我们能更愉快地保持沉默
that could make our aforementioned silence a little bit more comfortable.
我呢  想要一个iPod随身听
I mean, I, personally, request an iPod Shuffle.
装点后朋克啊  赶时髦乐队啊
You know, loaded with alt and post-punk, Depeche Mode,
灭迹乐队之类的歌
Erasure...
我想要悠忽饮料  还有无酒精含氟漱口水
And I need Yoo-hoo and ACT Fluoride Rinse for my teeth.
我想要个手机  带摄像头  谢谢
A cell phone. With a camera. Thank you.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
-谢谢  -好吧
- Thanks. - Okay.
你这招太他妈损了
You know, that's a fucking low blow,
就算是你这贱货  尼古拉斯   真的
even for a filthy sewer rat like you, Nichols. Really.
你告诉别人我有阴虱
You told people I have crabs.
你才发现啊
You just found out about that?
你这是作弊
It is cheating!
没事  罗瑞格兹在波士顿被砸时也没哭啊
Come on. A-Rod doesn't cry when he gets plunked in Beantown.
他还不是撑住了  去盗二垒
He sucks it up and tries to steal second.
我也想舔舔  上二垒啊
I've been trying to both suck and steal second,
要是大家都觉得我有阴虱我还怎么上啊
but I can't because everybody thinks I have cooties!
说到上垒  你多少分了
Speaking of a set, how many you got?
Thirty-six.
刚洗澡时刚给波克插了双指
After I gave Pirkle the double shocker in the showers just now.
真的  你上了波克
Really? You Pirkled?
是啊  一遍又一遍
Oh, I Pirkled and then I Pirkled again.
-感觉怎么样  -很粗糙
- And? - It was gnarly.
阴蒂好大
It's macroclit.
-就像给小孩口活似的  -我的天
- It was like blowing a toddler. - Oh, my God!
-很不舒服  -太他妈有劲了
- It was so uncomfortable. - That's fucking hilarious.
36  那我们俩打平了
Oh, God! So 36. We're tied.
-是的  -没错
- Yep. - Yeah.
-要不就到此为止吧  -要不别再玩儿了
- Hey, do you wanna just stop? - Have you considered maybe we just stop?
-我是无所谓啦  -你要想继续我也可以啊
- Because I could do that. - I don't have to but if you want to.
-因为我们都操了...  -不少了
- 'Cause we both fucked... - Lots.
还记得我们当初为什么要比这个么
Remind me why we did this to ourselves in the first place.
因为我无比好胜
Because I am insanely competitive.
而我因为上瘾所以得时刻满足需要
And I need to feed my addictive tendencies at all times.
吃饼干大赛
Cookie-eating contest?
你认识我吗
Son, have you ever actually seen me?
-你肯定会输  -滚开
- You are going down. - Get out...
谢谢大家  这是送给科拉的
Thanks, guys. That was for Cora.
我们会想念你的笑声  玉米狗  现在休息一会儿
We're gonna miss your laugh, Corndog. And we're gonna take five.
你来了  我们正好要休息一会儿
Hey! You made it! We're just going on break.
你看上去和平时不太一样
Wow. You look so different.
工作时我还是想比较正经点
Well, you know. I like to keep things profesh at work.
我给你在吧台留了个高位
I saved you a stool with a view.
其实我需要一张桌子
Actually, we're gonna need a table.
-我不知道你要来  -我说了这应该挺好玩的
- I didn't know you were coming. - You heard me say it sounded fun.
希望你不介意我跟别人提了你的演出
I hope you don't mind I told some of the guys about your show.
我差点赶不过来
I almost didn't make it.
现在卖方不肯划掉
Get this, the sellers are now refusing to drop
突发置换这一项
the replacement contingency!
你他妈能别提房子的事儿了吗
Would you shut up about real estate?
我当初要你搬进来你不肯
I asked you to move in with me and you said no.
所以你现在没资格说话
So you have no talking rights here.
不错  像双重约会
This is nice. Like a double date!
-我们不是一对  -我们不是一对
- We're not together. - We're not together.
我们还需要一把椅子
Actually we're gonna need another chair.
为什么
Why?
你看着像基佬
You look like the Gay Edge.
你好啊
Hey!
留位
就好像是  你更是你自己了  平时都是...
It's like you become more you. Which normally is like...
可是现在好了  那个人
But now it's okay... because the person, like,
不管是谁  他包容你的一切
whoever, they chose to take all that on.
所有奇奇怪怪的方面
All that weird stuff.
无论是不好的还是隐藏的特质
Whatever's wrong or bad or hiding in you.
突然都没关系了
Suddenly it's all right.
你不再觉得自己是个怪胎了
You don't feel like such a freak anymore.
莱瑞
Larry!
月亮敢这样吗
Would the moon do this?
我赢了
I won!
莱瑞  很高兴见到你
Larry! Good to see you, mate.
身上有些味道抱歉  刚宰了头鹿
Sorry about the stink. I killed a caribou!
腌在菠萝汁里野味就能淡点
Less gamey marinated in pineapple juice.
还让精液更美味
Also, makes your spunk taste good.
所以宝贝你有福了  这是什么
So you're in luck, babe! What's that?
这是...
Oh. It's, uh...
是帕波的东西
It's Piper's stuff.
哥们  一起吧  我们正要出去吃点拉面
Aw. Brother. Come on, we were just heading out for some ramen.
现在有保姆能偷点闲  东西让门童看着
You know, we have a babysitter! I'll leave these with the doorman.
不用了  皮特  我得...
No, Pete. Really, I should... I...
这可是情人节啊  混蛋  一起来
It's Valentine's Day, asshole! Come join us.
我在你垃圾桶里找到这个
I found this in your trash.
这是...
And this is...
你一直提起的那个人
the guy you always talking about?
我知道爱一个
Yeah, I know something about loving people
不知回报的人的滋味
who aren't smart enough to wanna be loved back.
但我知道个秘密  我告诉你
But I learned a secret that I can tell you.
他们都不值得爱
They don't deserve it.
他永久地毁了我的这个节日
He's ruined this day for me forever.
大家都不知道我们不在一起了
Nobody knows that we're not together.
可是你知道啊
Yeah, but you do.
-是  我知道  -对了
- I do. I do know. - Yeah.
你知道最疯狂的是什么吗
You know what is crazy?
就是经历了这一切一切
I still wanna believe in all of this stuff.
我还愿意相信这些东西
Even after everything that's happened.
-是不是很可悲  -不不
- Isn't that sad? - Oh, no.
我觉得这是勇敢
I think that's brave.
谢谢
Thank you.
说真的  你觉得我该隆胸吗
Seriously. Do you think I should get fake tits?
是的
Yeah. Probably.
伊恩
混蛋
Asshole.
你知道我最难过什么吗
You know what gets me?
我们在这里浪费了最美好的年华
We're wasting the best years of our lives in here.
我们的胸不会比现在更美
Like, our tits are never gonna look better.
我们的翘臀也不会比现在更美
Our asses are never gonna look better.
没人上我  没人吻我
You know, no one's touching my ass. No one's kissing my lips.
傻瓜  我来吻你
Shit. I'll kiss your dumb lips.
再来一次
Do it again.
-不行  -不行不行
- No! - No! No.
不行
No.
过来
Come here.
没事的
It's okay.
珀比  过来给她们看看什么才是真正的鬼步舞
Yo, P. Come and show these fools how to cabbage patch for real.
不用了
Nah. I'm good.
别装得什么事都没有一样
Man, don't act like everything fine. Like this...
行了  你吃千层面
Yo. I don't interrupt you
吃得正爽的时候我也没打搅过你啊
when you going to town on a bunch of spaghetti. Damn!
回你那维妈身边去好了
Yo, why don't you head on back to old Erykah Badu over there?
我就当没听见这句
I'm gonna forget you said that.
我又不在乎你听没听见
I don't give a fuck what you forget or remember!
妈逼这下好了  多谢啊
Oh, shit. Great! Thanks a lot, man.
你走开
You should leave.
珀比
Poussey!
这是我和你爸之间的事
This is between me and your father.
喂
Hey!
-喂  -干嘛
- Hey! - Well?
-我们不走  -跟美国人说去
- We're not leaving. - Talk to the Americans.
操你妈逼  你这个混蛋  都是你
Fuck you. Fuck you, man. This is your doing. You!
喝酒了吧  孩子
Been drinking, little girl?
珀比  别这样
Poussey, please.
你无权决定我的生活
You don't get to decide what happens to my life!
你没这个权利
Not you!
我爱她
I love her.
所以你必须回家
And that is why you're going home.
我受够了  我哪儿都不去
I'm done. I'm not going anywhere.
抱歉  中校
Pardon us, Oberstleutnant.
请继续享用冰激凌
Enjoy your ice cream.
你知道吗  现在有些治疗项目
You know, there are programs
可以纠正你女儿有问题的取向
that can change your daughter's confused predilections.
谢谢  但她没事
Thanks, but she's fine.
我的女士
My lady.
派对真有意思啊
Fun party.
没男人  没酒  没点像样的吃的  也没有粉
A party with no men, booze, real food or drugs.
还好我们年纪大了  无所谓了
Good thing we're too old for any trouble.
没错  花园捣腾得怎么样了
Right. How's the gardening going?
天气转暖  就能真正用了
Once the thaw comes, we'll really get going.
我本想喊你加入
Well, I'd ask you to join,
不过看着你有自己的事儿
but you clearly have your own hobbies.
我们得有人
We gotta have people.
你知道这样不会有善终
You know this will not end well.
你真笨
You're retarded.
你呢  查普曼
What about you, Chapman?
就好像一次漫长的旅途后  终于回家
It's like coming home after a long trip.
这就是爱
That's what love is like.
就像回家
It's like coming home.
谢谢你问我
Thanks for asking.